## Mohtasm Mohamed

#### Full Stack Developer

I am a professional web developer with over 5 years experience crafting modern, mobile-friendly websites., I'm interested in coding and writing command scripts. Interested in social networks, publishing scripts, business management, content management scripts such as Wordpress, Blogger, Android applications, and desktop applications.I'm very passionate about my design work and I'm confident I have the skills for a variety of projects.



mohtasmsawilh1@gmail.com 🔀

+201119195568

Zagazig, Egypt ♀

15 March, 1994 🏥

mohtasmbelah.com 🥌

linkedin.com/in/mohtasmsawilh in

mo3tasmbelah 🔕

facebook.com/mohtasm.sawilh

github.com/mohtasmsawilh []

mohtasmsawilh

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Back End Developer

01/2010 - 02/2013

I struggled for years but once coding clicked, I quickly learned and moved my way up a developer, software developer, Work with Team, I went to school, got my degree in computer science, system analysis and went looking for the job, the same story as everyone else college didn't prepare me for "real world"

# Front End Designer

09/2013 - 01/2015

Directing software development projects, producing, testing and debugging code.

## Full Stack Developer

07/2016 - Present

Leading engineers and developers, develop high-quality software design and architect-true identify, prioritize and execute tasks in the software development life cycle, Develop tools and applications by producing clean, efficient code automate tasks through appropriate tools and scripting, review and debug code, perform validation and verification testing, collaborate with internal teams and vendors to fix and improve products, document development phases and monitor systems, ensure software is up-to-date with latest technologies

### **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS**

Bachelor of Information Technology (2012 – 2016) Faculty Of Technology Al Azhar University

Higher Secondary School Certificate (2010 – 2012)

Secondary School Certificate (2007 – 2010)

Primary School (2001 – 2007)

Algehad Primary School

### **SKILLS**

Android App Development HTML5 & CSS

Angular / JavaScript / jQuery

Php & Mysql

Java

C#

Microsoft SQL Server

Microsoft Office

Photoshop

WordPress

Visual Studio

### **LANGUAGES**

Arabic

Engish

• •

### **INTERESTS**

Coder

Technology and growth

business

reading

traveling

foreign languages

community involvement

photography

3D Animation

designing